madcatz.com 2017-06-10

# Mad Catz Privacy Policy page | Mad Catz

### STATEMENT ON THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT (“Statement”)

Last Updated: May 29, 2013

### Personal Information

Mad Catz Interactive, Inc., its affiliates and/or subsidiary companies (collectively “Mad Catz”) operates this website. Mad Catz may ask you to register and provide personal information when you purchase products from our online store, download software, register new products, access product information, enter a contest or sweepstakes, sign into a page that requires authorization or when you engage in other activity that requires registration. Mad Catz may also collect credit card information to bill you for products that you have purchased.

The personal information that Mad Catz collects may include your name, your e-mail address, your user ID, your domain name, your URL, your mailing address, your credit card information, and/or your telephone number. Mad Catz may also collect demographic information such as your age, gender, zip code/postal code, education level, household income, the operating system you use, your preferences, interests, favorites, and whether you are a personal or business user. If you choose not to register and provide this information, you can still use most of Mad Catz’s website. Unfortunately, you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

### Children’s Personal Information

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under the age of 13. If we are made aware that we have such personal information, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information.

### Computer and Device Information

As you access our websites or install and use our software or game content, we may collect device-specific information from you (such as your hardware model, the operating system version, and other unique device identifiers). Specifically, this information may include such things as your IP address, your cookie information, your globally unique identifier information, operating system information, a description of any Mad Catz products connected to your PC or other device and how such products are used, your browser type, your domain names, the times and dates that you access our websites, the service provider you use and/or the identify of any referring websites.

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

### Personal Information

With your permission, Mad Catz collects, and uses your personal information to enhance your use of our websites, products and services. This allows us to serve you better by alerting you to things that might be of interest to you including, product and website updates, special offers, promotions, newsletter information, new product announcements, events, contests and much more. This also allows us to invite you to participate in surveys. Mad Catz may use this information to communicate with you either via social networking, e-mail, online chat, mail or telephone only after you have agreed upon this form of communication. Password reminders are an exception to this rule as an email will only be sent when requested.

We also use anonymous data to create statistics and reports for various business purposes. We may share anonymous data with marketing partners in order to improve our content and services.

We occasionally hire third party companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as delivery of email blasts, providing customer support, processing transactions and performing statistical analysis. Mad Catz will only provide those companies with the minimally required personal information (such as e-mail address) that they need. These third party companies are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

### Computer and Device Information

We use the information we collect from you to enhance the services we provide and to maintain, protect and improve such services, develop new services, and to protect Mad Catz and our users. We also use this information to offer you tailored content. We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services.

### E-Mail Messaging

Mad Catz will periodically send our registered users e-mail messages about our products, events, software updates, etc. When sending you e-mail, we may use pixel tags that allows us to format messages tailored to your computer’s capabilities. We also use this technology to determine, how many people open our e-mails. When you click on a link within an e-mail, you are redirected to the Internet. We then log whether you accessed the link.

### Disclosure of Information

Mad Catz keeps your personally identifiable information confidential. We do not disclose it to third parties or others that do not have a need of such information except under certain circumstances as set forth below.

Examples of instances where Mad Catz may share your personal information include the following:

  * Information used for external processing, which allows our affiliates, subsidiaries and third party service providers to provide and improve the services we provide to you.
  * Information that you post to our websites, such as our forums, social networking sites and comment forms may be used at our discretion for any lawful purpose.
  * If the information is needed to protect the rights or property of Mad Catz, including its websites.
  * If the information is needed for legal reasons, e.g., to respond to legal requests or if we believe that disclosure is required to investigate illegal activities, fraud, physical threats to you or others, national security threats or as otherwise required by any applicable law or regulation.

### Control & Review of Your Personal Information

After you have completed registration on any of the Mad Catz websites, you may stop the delivery of future communications from Mad Catz to you, including newsletters, special offers and updates at any time by simply unsubscribing to such services. Each email you receive contains instructions explaining how to stop receiving such e-mails. You may also contact us at privacy@madcatz.com to opt-out.

### Protection of Information

Mad Catz uses industry-standard security techniques on the Mad Catz websites to help protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we collect from you. When you access your account information or transmit personally identifiable data to the Mad Catz websites, that information is stored on servers that the Mad Catz has attempted to secure from unauthorized access or intrusion. When you access our sites, “Secure Socket Layer” software encrypts the personal information you transmit. Mad Catz cannot be and is not responsible for unauthorized access to information by hackers or others who have obtained such access through illegal measures.

“Phishing” is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it might be from Mad Catz asking for your personal information, do not respond. Mad Catz would not request your password, user name, credit card information, or other personal information through e-mail.

If you have questions or complaints regarding this Statement, please contact us at privacy@madcatz.com with any questions or concerns. All customer complaints will be formally reviewed by Mad Catz.

### Changes to This Statement

Mad Catz may occasionally update this Statement. If and when Mad Catz updates this Statement, the revised date will be displayed. Mad Catz encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Mad Catz is protecting your information.

Thank you for your interest in Mad Catz, its products and services.
